

Feros
Djahani
Front-End Developer
(Industrial Mechanic)

Feros Djahani Marie Juchacz Straß

Marie Juchacz Straße 42a 52349, Düren

0049/17645812584

E-Mail:

f.djahani@outlook.de

Portfolio:

www.feros-djahani.developerakademie.net

About Me

I am a German-speaking Front-End Developer with experience in building web apps with JavaScript & Angular, as well as React and Vue.js. You can find my projects that including responsive websites and business apps in my public portfolio. I started my IT journey by coding small websites at home and watching other tutorials. During my current job as an industrial mechanic, I found that the part of work I enjoyed the most was always related to software. So I decided to amplify my IT knowledge and gain experience in web development. I am looking forward to building on my experience and starting my career in IT as a junior developer position.

Main Stack:

Side Stack:

Git, APIs (REST), Google Firebase

- JavaScript
- TypeScript, Angular
- React
- Vue.js
- HTML, CSS, Bootstrap

Skills

- Top Motivated: : During the Days in the Week I had to work on a full-time job and after a day at work I went to my computer to code at night and also through the weekends. I have a history of doing a good job, so if it gets hard or if it is no fun, I do not complain.
- Building Applications with JavaScript & Angular: I built landing pages and several web apps, as well as OOP-based Jump-and-Run-Games with the respective technologies.
- Working in a Software Team: During learning coding, I did several group projects where I learned how to develop a software project in a
- **High sense of responsibility:** I am used to taking responsibility and working diligently, as I always did in my job as an industrial mechanic

Professional Experience

Young Capital / Telephone Account Manager

JAN 2022 - PRESENT, Home-Office

- Handling individual customer calls
- Responsibility for regular KPI-Report to management

Industrial Mechanic / Temp Agencies

(Go Work Solutions, Zeitfuchs, AMB Zeitarbeit, etc.)

NOV 2020 - NOV 2021

- Manufacturing of components according to customer requirements
- Maintenance work on the individual machines

RWE Power AG / Industrial Mechanic

AUG 2016 - AUG 2020, NIEDERAUßEM COLOGN

- Repair machine components
- Weld individual assemblies together
- Safe handling of the operation of necessary machines in the production process.

Education

Developer Akademie / JavaScript & Angular Web Development

Training

NOV 2021 - DEC 2022, Munich

Project based coding academy. Main Stack: JavaScript, Angular

Portfolio: www.feros-djahani.developerakademie.net

Extensive Coding School, Learning Front-End Development, Coding, Agile Project Management, and building several projects in teams and alone.

RWE Power AG/IHK Cologne/ Industrial Mechanic Training

AUG 2016 - AUG 2020, NIEDERAUßEM COLOGNE

- Theoretical and practical introduction to the operation of individual machines
- Theoretical and practical introduction to several work processes such as turning, milling, and welding
- Intensive preparation for the theoretical and practical final exam

Languages

German: native

English: fluent

Farsi: fluent